César **Zavala López**

Web developer

CONTACT



834 198 2974



cesarzavalamx15@gmail.com



cesarzavala.tech

EDUCATION

Programming Technician ITACE

2017- 2020

Information Technology Engineer Universidad Politécnica de Victoria

2020 - 2023

ABILITIES

PHP BOOTSTRAP 5

SQL LARAVEL 10

HTML TAILWINDS CSS

FIGMA ADOBE XD

SKILLS

TOEFL (English B2)

Capacity to adapt to new technologies

Strong auto-learning skills

Results Orientation

ABOUT ME

Recently graduated in Information Technology Engineering, my passion lies in web application development. Specialized in LARAVEL, I excel in building solutions from backend to frontend. I use Bootstrap for agile projects and Tailwind CSS for more elaborate initiatives. I have a solid foundation in relational databases.

EXPERIENCES

VOLUNTEER WORK

Un Cachito de Luz A.C. I Cd. Victoria/Tamaulipas

2017 - 2022

Designed a database and donation delivery capture system for medications using Visual Basic.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ITACE | Cd. Victoria/Tamaulipas

FEB 2020 - MAR 2020

Designed and developed a .NET application programmed in Visual Basic for attendance registration using QR codes. The application also sends alerts to parents regarding the entry and exit activities of their children at the institution.

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Cactu Nieves I Cd. Victoria/Tamaulipas

MAR 2022 - APR 2022

JAN 2022 - FEB 2022

Designed, developed, and implemented a .NET application programmed in C# for managing sales processes and administration within the company.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SVAM international I Cd. Victoria/Tamaulipas

Created and executed the update of the interface for the LEADS web application, using Bootstrap 5 and incorporating Datatables and Google Charts.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

UPV I Cd. Victoria/Tamaulipas

SEP 2023 - DEC 2023

Designed and developed an application in LARAVEL and FLASK in conjunction with ARDUINO for facial recognition attendance for students at the Polytechnic University of Victoria. The project is currently in the internal implementation process at the institution.

CERTIFICATIONS

CCNA: Switching, Routing, and Wireless Essentials

Cisco I MAR 2022

Introduction to Cybersecurity

Cisco | JUL 2022

Google User Experience (UX) Design Certificate

Coursera | OCT 2023